



Bekasi, Indonesia | +62 89643653277

evasagitaputri99@gmail.com | linkedin.com/in/eva-sagita-putri-3b52431b6/

# **SUMMARY**

I'm Eva Sagita Putri, a 7<sup>th</sup> semester accounting student at Gunadarma University. I'm interested work in accounting, finance, taxation, and administration. I'am a hard worker, dicipline and like to learn new things. I have had an internship as Admin experience in AJB Bumiputera 1912 and PT Solusimaxi Consulting and Training. I have also been a volunteer experience as a Tax Volunteer for KPP Depok Cimanggis, my job is to assist and provide direction to taxpayers who report taxes using e-filing and e-form.

## **EDUCATION**

#### **GUNADARMA UNIVERSITY**

2018- Present

Undergraduate of Economic, Accounting

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### PERUSAHAAN AJB BUMIPUTERA 1912

Des 2021 – Feb 2022

#### **Admin**

- 1. Filling and documentation nasabah.
- 2. Carry out administrative processes and communication with nasabah.
- 3. Input the customer's insurance policy claim.
- 4. Create a letter Antaran Habis Kontrak and Penebusan in Microsof Excel

#### PT. SOLUSI MAXI CONSULTING AND TRAINING

Jan - March 2020

### **Sales Marketing**

- 1. Promote types of ISO training.
- 2. Offering ISO Series training services to Customers.
- 3. Active in Finding target customers at least 10 customer in 1 month.

## **VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE**

BUMI FOUNDATION Sept- Des 2020

### **Divisi Digital Campeigner**

- Manage social media accounts.
- Create attractive concepts to motivate social change.
- Planning contenct and creating interactive post.
- Planning for content through social media.
- Manage and coordinate social media input from the team.

Beasiswa Titik Nol August 2021

## **Volunteer Campaign Online Nasional**

- Post campaign what is scholarship via social media.
- Planning for content through social media.
- Create a national campaign through social media.

#### **DJP JAWA BARAT III**

## **Tax Volunteer for KPP Depok Cimanggis**

Sept 2021 – March 2022

- Assist and provide direction to tax payers who report taxes using e-filling and e-form.
- Reporting the annual SPT through e-filling the KPP

### **ADDITIONAL**

Technical: Ms. Word, Excel, PowerPoint, Zahir

Language: Bahasa Indonesia and English

Interpersonal Skills: Team work, Communication, Strong analytical, Problem solving, and

Time Management.

Interest: Accounting, Finance, Taxation, and Administration.

## **Certifications and Training:**

- GUNADARMA UNIVERSITY
  - Corporate Income Taxes, and Brevet A
- ZAHIR INTERNASIONAL
  - Zahir User Certified